# Katrina Judd

#### **Administrative Professional**

Burleson, TX 76028 katrinajudd4\_xdh@indeedemail.com 817-240-5955

Highly organized and budget conscious professional with over 12+ years of experience identifying opportunities for improved inventory management and reducing purchasing budgets to increase revenue. Passionate about accuracy, efficiency, and delivering superior products in a timely manner. Multi-Skilled and resourceful administrator with excellent track record of delivering a wide variety of clerical services and applying general administrative and departmental policies company wide. Possess strong expertise on inventory management, purchasing, accounts payable, data analysis, customer service, vendor relations and correspondence handling.

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

# Work Experience

# Administrative Assistant (Material Acquisitions, Inventory Control, Accounts Payable, AR)

R2 Fabrication, LLC - Fort Worth, TX December 2016 to February 2020

- Material Acquisitions
- Create vendor purchase orders and enter invoices into accounting system.
- Setup new vendors utilizing W-9 form information.
- Process the companies weekly check run. Fold and mail checks to vendors.
- AR Billings/Invoices and Aging Report reconciliation.
- Monthly bank statement reconciliation.
- Bank deposit using desktop check scanner.
- Greeted visitors, answered phones, distributed mail, ordered office supplies, as well as other clerical duties.

#### **Laboratory Technician**

Nalco Champion Technologies - Cresson, TX November 2013 to April 2016

#### Oil & Gas)

- Logged Samples for various testing.
- Gas Chromatography
- ION Chromatography
- ICP MS
- · Data Analysis and Reporting.
- LIMS Software
- Ordered Lab Supplies.
- Monthly Expense Report.

#### **Inventory Control Clerk**

Millard Refrigerated Services - Fort Worth, TX June 2013 to November 2013

- Daily Cycle Counts.
- Research and resolve inventory discrepancies.
- Data Analysis and Reporting.

#### **Reverse Logistics Expert**

PSS World Medical - Grand Prairie, TX February 2011 to September 2012

- Processed all customer returns and recalls.
- Vendor Relations
- Inventory Control
- Customer Service

#### **Computer Operator**

Core-Mark International - Fort Worth, TX March 2005 to July 2010

Reverse Logistics, Inventory Control, AR, Customer Service)

- Processed customer returns and recalls.
- Cycle Count
- Vendor Relations
- Customer Relations
- · Ad-hoc/Daily Reporting
- Logistics
- Bank Deposits using desktop scanner. Armored pick up.
- AR Billings/Invoices
- Internal Auditing
- Scanned, filed, faxed, archived documents, as well as other misc. clerical duties.

#### **TOOLS**

- Excel
- Access
- Word
- Outlook
- Foundation Construction Accounting Software
- QuickBooks
- EDI Systems
- JDE One World Explorer
- AS400
- LIMS
- Google Dropbox
- OneNote
- Teams

### Education

# **High school or equivalent**

#### Skills

- Inventory Management (10+ years)
- Purchasing (4 years)
- Accounts Payable (4 years)
- Accounts Receivable (4 years)
- Customer Service & Relations (10+ years)
- Vendor Relations (4 years)
- Data Entry (10+ years)
- 10-Key (10+ years)
- Filing & Data Archiving (5 years)
- Logistics (2 years)
- Problem Solving (10+ years)
- Telephone Reception (4 years)
- Administrative Assistance (6 years)
- AP (4 years)
- Quickbooks (Less than 1 year)
- Vendor Management (4 years)
- Collections (3 years)
- Invoicing (4 years)

#### Links

http://www.linkedin.com/in/katrina-judd-429250131

#### Assessments

#### Sales: Influence & Negotiation — Proficient

February 2020

Persuading reluctant customers to buy products or services, and influencing and negotiating with customers to meet sales goals.

Full results: <a href="https://share.indeedassessments.com/">https://share.indeedassessments.com/</a>

share to profile/3663f973d52eba6e6bfd41384072436aeed53dc074545cb7

## **Conscientiousness — Highly Proficient**

February 2020

Tendency to be well-organized, rule-abiding, and hard-working.

Full results: <a href="https://share.indeedassessments.com/">https://share.indeedassessments.com/</a>

share\_to\_profile/41d52e5f733d336a9ac4124727a9a765eed53dc074545cb7

### **Teamwork: Interpersonal Skills — Highly Proficient**

February 2020

Resolving disputes, solving team problems, and understanding nonverbal cues.

Full results: https://share.indeedassessments.com/share to profile/

f1bf88020d79cd1a81199adf8243f65eeed53dc074545cb7

# **Administrative Assistant — Familiar**

February 2020

Using basic scheduling, attention to detail, and organizational skills in an office setting.

Full results: <a href="https://share.indeedassessments.com/">https://share.indeedassessments.com/</a>

share to profile/33ddd571fc2a0484d2fd8431fcd4e799eed53dc074545cb7

Indeed Assessments provides skills tests that are not indicative of a license or certification, or continued development in any professional field.

#### Additional Information

- Inventory Management
- Purchasing
- Accounts Payable
- Accounts Receivable
- Customer Service & Relations
- Vendor Relations
- Data Entry
- 10-Key
- Filing & Data Archiving
- Logistics
- Problem Solving
- Telephone Reception
- Administrative Assistance